### Contact

9000638632 (Mobile) swasakamanoj@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ manojswasaka (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

**Data Structures** Service-Oriented Architecture (SOA) SQL

### Certifications

Neo4j Certified Professional Bronze Appsec Titan

# Manoj Swasaka

Senior Associate at DBS Bank

Hvderabad

## Summary

Experienced Java Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in REST, SOAP, ECS, Spring Boot, Apache Camel, and Jenkins. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science from Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University.

# Experience

**DBS Bank** 

1 year 10 months

Senior Associate

February 2021 - Present (4 months)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

#### Associate

August 2019 - February 2021 (1 year 7 months)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Phenom People

**Product Development Engineer** 

September 2018 - August 2019 (1 year)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

### Mize

Java Developer

September 2015 - August 2018 (3 years)

### KMP IT SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED

Jr. Java Developer

July 2014 - September 2015 (1 year 3 months)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

### Education

Birla Institute of Technology and Science, Pilani Master of Technology - MTech, Data Science and Engineering · (2019 - 2021)

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2009 - 2013)